<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-15T23:06:25-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Felipe Borges</title><subtitle>Blogging about tech and maybe some more stuff.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">First Post (IS IT THOUGH?!)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/15/first-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Post (IS IT THOUGH?!)" /><published>2020-06-15T00:00:00-03:00</published><updated>2020-06-15T00:00:00-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/15/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/15/first-post.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;alright-here-we-go&quot;&gt;Alright, here we go&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is probably the third/fourth blog I’m trying to run. It’s funny, because I didn’t even get to write my fourth post. My blogs just died out of my laziness. Funny, I just remembered the following (((LOSS))) posted in a Facebook group full of people pretending to be ants:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/builditagain.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Then we build it again&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s pretty much it, fellas. &lt;strong&gt;Then we build it again&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, my first urge was to put a lot of work into customizing this blog, but that’s pretty much useless if I don’t even get to write as many as 2 blog posts :sweat:. So I’m &lt;em&gt;Keeping It Simple, Stupid&lt;/em&gt;, at least until I manage to get some work done here. I’m not worrying about meta tags. I’m not worried about SEO. I’m not even worried about a fucking icon. I just want to write something. Buuut, I’m curious mind with ADHD, so expect me to play around with tinkles and twinkles of some blogging plugins that I may find somewhere (on GitHub). It’s funny, I’m writing all of this shit like anyone would care, which probably isn’t the case, but idc, because I have started the journey through my twenties learning to enjoy myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have fun, take risks, but don’t lose your mind. Peace &amp;amp; love :hearts:&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Felipe</name></author><summary type="html">Alright, here we go</summary></entry></feed>